Waco Civic Theatre records, Inclusive: 1931-2002, undated, Bulk: 1955-1995, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Waco Civic Theatre records
Inclusive: 1931-2002, undated, Bulk: 1955-1995, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
2231
Waco Civic Theatre, 1925 -
11 document boxes 2 OVZ document boxes 7 OVZ boxes 1 OVZ folder
The Waco Civic Theatre records document business operations and performances of the community volunteer theatre group from 1931-2020. Notable documents include minutes, programs, scrapbooks, photographs, clippings, and correspondence.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The Waco Little Theatre was established in the 1920s and performed for a Waco audience from 1925 to 1936. The group went dormant until 1945 when Paul Baker, then Professor and Chair of the Baylor University Drama Department, worked with former members of the Little Theatre to create and charter the Waco Civic Theatre, Inc. The charter was granted by the State of Texas for 50 years, beginning in 1948.
In 1948, the Waco Civic Theater (WCT) began performing at Baylor University’s Little Theater and did so until budget cuts and increased productions at Baylor disallowed the use of facilities in 1951. WCT began performing in other places around Waco including Casa Blanca, the Shrine Ballroom, the National Guard Armory, and YWCA until a permanent home was established in 1958. Paul Baker worked with renowned theatre designer, James Hull Miller, to create the building on Lake Air Drive in Waco. In 1963 the building was commended by the Journal of the Royal Institute of British Architects. Since then, the building has undergone several additions and renovations.
Waco Civic Theatre currently produces six plays per year, including children’s productions. Local partnerships also allow the WCT to coordinate children’s theatre workshops and outreach programs. The WCT is currently a non-profit organization and receives funding through ticket sales, and has received several grants and donations from sources such as the Cooper Foundation, Waco Foundation, and an endowment funded by Frank Baird, Jr. of Buffalo, New York, in honor of his mother Mrs. Flora Cameron Baird.
Scope and Content
The Administrative series includes by-laws, correspondence, production materials, and minutes of the Waco Civic Theatre. Minutes are photocopies as the originals were retained by the organization. Production folders include information such as licensing for names, rights, music, and scripts in addition to seating information, ticket sales information, other financial records, press releases, contracts, correspondence, cast lists, and call sheets. Correspondence by Hilton H. Howell documents the construction of the Waco Civic Theatre building in the 1950s. Several folders also hold reference and design materials for the build in consultation with famed theater designer James Hull Miller.
The Publications series is primarily clippings, newsletters, and programs. The clippings include reviews, advertisements, and write-ups about the productions. Newsletters are under two names, “The Prompter” and “Upstaged.” They both document performances, announce upcoming auditions, and highlight the work of the theatre. Programs document the Waco Little Theatre from 1931-1936 and the Waco Civic Theatre from 1950-2002. There are also articles about Paul Baker.
The Scrapbooks and Audiovisual series comprise the bulk of the collection. The scrapbooks document a range of performances over forty years through photographs, programs, clippings, and other items. The Audiovisual series includes many photo negatives, photo slides, and photographs, in addition to a few audiocassettes, 16mm film reels, and reel to reel tapes. For the most part, negatives and slides are undated but, in some cases, correspond with photographs. Photographs often include multiple shows within a folder, this is recognized in folder titles by including show names and the month the show was performed. Several hand drawn oversize posters are also included. It is unclear whether these were used as decorations for the theatre or as part of a performance.
Arrangement
Materials were organized prior to this most recent processing. Audiovisual materials had been rehoused by type, scrapbooks were in oversize boxes, and other materials had new boxes. There was no discernible arrangement for written documents. Currently, the records are in four series: I. Administrative, II. Publications, III. Scrapbooks, and IV. Audiovisual.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 2231. Acquired 1981-04-10
Related Resources
Related references
“About WCT.” Waco Civic Theatre. Accessed 2020 October 2.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Baker, Paul, 1911-2009.; Miller, James Hull
Subjects (Organizations)
Waco Civic Theatre.
Subjects
Theater --Texas -- Waco.; Theater architecture.
Genres
16mm (photographic film size).; Audiocassettes.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Minutes (Records); Negatives (Photographs); Newsletters.; Open reel audiotapes.; Photographs.; Programs.; Scrapbooks.; Slides (photographs); Theater programs.
- Administrative, 1950-2002, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Administrative series, dated 1950-2002, includes by-laws, minutes, correspondence, production materials, and information on the design and construction of the Civic Theatre building. The series is arranged alphabetically and in good condition.
  - By-Laws, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Children’s Theatre Academy, circa 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Contracts & Legal Proceedings, 1952-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: General, 1950-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Hilton H. Howell, President, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Theatre Design & Construction, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes [Copies], 1957-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New Year’s Eve Gala, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Production Folder: You’ve Come a Long Way Baby, circa 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Production Folder: Summer Melodrama, circa 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Production Folder: Little Shop of Horrors, 1995 May (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Production Folder: Dirty Work at the Crossroads, 1995 July (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Production Folder: The Sound of Music, 1995 September (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Production Folder: Driving Miss Daisy, 1995 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Production Folder: Annie, 1995 December (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Production Folder: The Royal Family, circa 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Production Folder: Lost in Yonkers, 1996 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Production Folder: Nunsense II, 1996 May (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Production Folder: Bye Bye Birdie, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Production Folder: The Murder at the Wedding [Dinner Theatre], circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Stage Management Workshop, Fay McClinton, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Tax Exemption, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Theatre Design & Construction: General, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Theatre Design & Construction: James Hull Miller (1 of 3), 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Theatre Design & Construction: James Hull Miller (2 of 3), 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Theatre Design & Construction: James Hull Miller (3 of 3), 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Theatre Design & Construction: Loft Addition Specifications, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Theatre Design & Construction: Paint Bids, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Waco Civic Theatre Guild Member Lists, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Youth Theatre, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Publications, 1931-2002, undated; 2
  The Publications series, dated 1931-2020, is composed primarily of clippings, newsletters, advertising materials, and theatre programs. The series is arranged alphabetically and is in good condition.
  - Clippings, 1958-1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1992-1998, 2020 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mailers & Advertising, 1965-circa 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters: The Prompter, 1964-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters: Upstaged, 1980-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Programs, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Programs: Actor Biographies, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Programs: Waco Little Theatre, 1931-1936 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Programs: The Civic Music Association, 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1950, 1956-1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1996-2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Paul Baker, 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Southwest Theatre Conference Membership Directory, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Scrapbooks, 1950-1992; 3
  The Scrapbooks series, dated 1950-1992, documents performances and the theatre through photographs, programs, and clippings. The series is arranged in chronological order and is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print
  - Untitled, 1950 May-1955 May (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1958 October-1959 September (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1959 November-1960 November (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1963 June-1965 May, 1966 February (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1964 June-1969 April (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Frank Baird Youth Theatre, 1968 September-1970 July (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1970 June-1974 September (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1974 Summer-1980 Summer (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - You Can’t Take It with You and Dracula, 1980 September-1984 May (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Untitled, 1984 May-1987 June (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1987 September-1990 August (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1992 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 4)
- Audiovisual, 1958-1996, undated; 4
  The Audiovisual series is dated 1958-1996 with a good amount of undated materials. The series is arranged alphabetically by media type, then chronologically within each medium. Media includes 16 mm film, audiocassettes, negatives, photographs, posters, reel to reels, and slides. The series is in good condition.
  16 mm motion picture film; 35 mm negative film (color); 35 mm slide; Photographic print; Reel to reel tapes
  - 16mm: untitled, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Audiocassette: Freedom Frolic, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Negatives: Bus Stop, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Negatives: Cinderella, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Negatives: Design for Murder, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Negatives: The Dining Room, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Negatives: Gunfight at Gory Gulch, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Negatives: Hasty Heart, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Negatives: House of Blue Leaves, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Negatives: Known People, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Negatives: Known Productions, Snow White and Sunshine Boys, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Negatives: The Loud Red Patrick, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Negatives: The Male Animal, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Negatives: The Odd Couple, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Negatives: ParisEL?, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Negatives: Pure as the Driven Snow, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Negatives: Rosie’s Ricochet Romance, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Negatives: Sabrina Fair, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Negatives: Take Her She’s Mine and The Importance of Being Earnest, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Negatives: Unknown Productions, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Negatives: Unknown Productions (8,9, and 10), undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Negatives: Wait Until Dark, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Negatives: Waco Civic Theatre Reception, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Negatives: Girls in 509, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Negatives: Who Were Those Girls I Saw You With?, 1960 May (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Negatives: Barefoot in the Park, 1967 October (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Negatives: Untitled, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Negatives: Adaptation & Next, Black Comedy, Forty Carats, and Come Blow Your Horn, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Negatives: Last of the Red Hot Lovers, Butterflies are Free, and Gamma Rays, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Negatives: How the Other Half Loves, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Negatives: Mrs. Reardon Drinks a Little, A Thousand Clowns, January Thaw, Unknown Production, and Night Watch, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Negatives: Prisoner of 2nd Ave, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Negatives: Finishing Touches, 1975 January (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Negatives: Here Lies Jeremy Troy, 1975 September (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Negatives: Mary, Mary & Sabrina, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Negatives: Rebel’s Revenge, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Negatives: God’s Favorite, 1977 May (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Negatives: The Marriage-Go-Round, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Negatives: Any Wednesday, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Negatives: To Kill A Mockingbird, 1981 September (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Negatives: The Pitfalls of Pauline, 1982 June (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Negatives: Rebel’s Revenge, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Negatives: Arsenic & Old Lace, 1984 November (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Negatives: No Sex Please We’re British, Seven Year Itch, and Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Negatives: Light up the Sky, 1988 May (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Negatives: The Nerd, 1988 September (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Negatives: Here Lies Jeremy Troy, 1989 November (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Negatives: The Curious Savage, 1990 January (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Negatives: Mass Appeal, 1990 February (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Negatives: To Kill a Mockingbird, 1990 March (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Negatives: Foxfire, 1991 March (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Negatives: Steel Magnolias, 1991 May (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Negatives: Cabaret, 1991 September (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Negatives: The Lion in Winter, 1991 November (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Teahouse of the August Moon, 1958 May (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Photographs: Time Limit, 1958 September (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Separate Tables and Bus Stop, 1959 February, September (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Photographs: The Remarkable Mr. Pennypacker, 1959 May (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: Arms and the Man, 1960 November (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Photographs: Girls in 509, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Photographs: Monique, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Photographs: Who Were Those Girls I Saw You With?, 1960 May (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Photographs: Ugly Duckling, Knives of Syria, and Marriage Proposal, 1961 November (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Photographs: Harvey, 1962 November (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Photographs: Rebel’s Revenge, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Photographs: The Pleasure of His Company and The Gazebo, 1964 April, May (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Photographs: Everybody Loves Opal and Never Too Late, 1965 April, September (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Photographs: General, 1965-1966, 1982 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: The Curious Savage; Mary, Mary; and Reluctant Debutante, 1966 May, September, November (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Night Must Fall, Absence of a Cello, Any Wednesday, Barefoot in the Park, and A Thousand Clowns, 1967 January, March, May, September, November (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Barefoot in the Park, 1967 October (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: The Subject was Roses, Affairs of State, Odd Couple, & The Impossible Years, 1968 January, March, May, November (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Star-Spangled Girl, Catch Me If You Can (March), A Roomful of Roses, and Fair Game, 1969 January, March, May, November (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: The American Dream, You Know I Can’t Hear You When the Water’s Running, Lo and Behold, Roar Like a Dove, and Wait until Dark, 1970 January, March, May, September, November (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Flower, Private Lives, Cactus and Lullaby, 1971 January, March, September (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Come Blow Your Horn, Angel Street, Black Comedy, Forty Carats, Adaptation and Next, 1972 January, March, May, September, November (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Come Blow Your Horn, 1972 January (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Butterflies Are Free, Last of the Red Hot Lovers, and Gamma Rays & The Savage Dilemma, 1973 January, May, November (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: The Savage Dilemma, 1973 November (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Loves & Kisses (May), Peril on the Brazos or Gunfight at Gory Gulch, January Thaw, Mrs. Reardon Drinks a Little, Night Watch (November) & Unknown Shows, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: How the Other Half Loves, 1974 January (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: ParisEL?, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Finishing Touches, 1975 January (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Prisoner of 2nd Avenue, 1975 May (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Rosie’s Ricochet Romance or the Road to Run, 1975 June (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Here Lies Jeremy Troy, 1975 September (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: The Odd Couple, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Mary, Mary; Unknown Show; and Sabrina, 1976 March, September, November (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Rebel’s Revenge, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Photographs: The Marriage Go Around, 1977 January (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photographs: God’s Favorite, 1977 May (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photographs: The Loud Red Patrick, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Candle-Light, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photographs: Any Wednesday, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Any Wednesday, and Kiss and Tell, 1978 January, September (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Photographs: The Price, 1978 November (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: The Silver Whistle, Arms & the Man, The Perils of Pomona, Jenny Kissed Me, 1979 March, May, June, September (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Photographs: The Perils of Pomona, 1979 June (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: The Little Foxes, Best of Friends, Barefoot in the Park, Peril on the Brazos or Gunfight at Gory Gulch, You Can’t Take It with You, 1980 January, March, May, June, September (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Brighton Beach Memoirs, 1980 February (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Dracula, the Vampire Play; The Second Time Around; Murder at the Howard Johnson’s; and Rosie’s Ricochet Romance, 1981 January, March, May, June (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: To Kill a Mockingbird, 1981 September (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Chapter Two, 1981 November (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: The Bishop Misbehaves, The Pitfalls of the Pauline, A Flea in Her Ear, The Member of the Wedding, 1982 January, June October, November (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Charley’s Aunt, 1982 May (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Lunch Hour, 1983 March (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: How Green Was My Brownie, 1983 April (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Hasty Heart, 1984 January (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: The Mousetrap, The Rainmaker, and Rebel’s Revenge, 1984 March, April, June (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: The Dining Room, 1984 September (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Arsenic & Old Lace, 1984 November (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Madison Cooper’s “Sironia, Texas”, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, No Sex Please We’re British, Seven Year Itch, and The Miner’s Daughter, 1985 January, May, September (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Inherit the Wind, 1986 January (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: God’s Favorite, The Skin of Our Teeth, Dirty Work at the Crossroads, & The Man Who Came to Dinner, 1986 March, May, June, November (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: The Remarkable Mr. Pennypacker, 1986 September (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Bus Stop, 1987 March (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: The Curse of Pomona, and A Gown of His Mistress, 1987 June, September (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Photographs: The Foreigner, 1987 November (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Photographs: Bell, Book & Candle, and The Unvarnished Truth, 1988 January, April (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Photographs: Light Up the Sky, 1988 May (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Lily the Felon’s Daughter, 1988 July (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Photographs: The Nerd, 1988 September (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Cedric, 1988 October (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Photographs: Design for Murder, 1988 October (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: The Best Christmas Pageant Ever, 1988 December (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: The Trip to Bountiful (1 of 3), 1989 February (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: The Trip to Bountiful (2 of 3), 1989 February (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: The Trip to Bountiful (3 of 3), 1989 February (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Play It Again, Sam, 1989 March (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Fallen Angels, 1989 April (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: The 1940s Radio Hour, 1989 May (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Pure as the Driven Snow or A Working Girl’s Secret, 1989 June (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Annie, 1989 September (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Here Lies Jeremy Troy, 1989 November (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: General, circa 1900-circa 1996 (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: The Curious Savage, 1990 January (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Mass Appeal, 1990 February (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: To Kill a Mockingbird, 1990 March (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Broadway Bound, 1990 May (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Gunfight at Gory Gulch or Peril on the Brazos, 1990 June (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: You Can’t Take It with You, 1991 January (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Fox Fire, 1991 March (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Steel Magnolias, 1991 May (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Cabaret, 1991 September (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: The Lion in Winter, 1991 November (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Deadwood Dick or Game of Gold, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: House of Blue Leaves, On Golden Pond, Deadwood Dick, and The Royal Family, 1992 January, March, July, November (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: House of Blues Leaves, 1992 January (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: The Music Man, 1992 September (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: The Foreigner, and The Rebel’s Revenge, 1993 January, June (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Nunsense, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Rumors, 1994 March (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Lend Me a Tender, and A Bad Day at Gopher’s Breath, 1994 June, July (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: The Royal Family, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Sound of Music, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)